Any stock specific strategy you
want to recommend.
I have two stocks on my radar for today.  The
first stock will be Wipro.  Look, yesterday
we saw that almost all time high was
closed.  I feel that we may
see good momentum in IT stocks today.
So out of that Wipro will be
my buy recommendation for today and
targets will be made at 220 and 225, trade can be done
for today and stop loss should be maintained at
202 in Wipro.  The second stock
will be Titan.  If we look at Titan,
consolidation has been happening for the last two-three days.  A
breakout is clearly visible.
A good rise can be seen in today's trading session.  It would
also be advisable to buy Titan Titan.
But the above targets will be made, you
can buy for the targets of 465 and 4650.
Stop loss should be maintained at Rs 4400.
So, you have to keep these in mind and
you are recommending a buy in Titan at 4650 with a stop loss of 4400.  Let's give a
welcome back.  You are watching today's market and
let us now talk about stock specific
and Harish, the results of ICICI Lobar have come, the
combined ratio has shown improvement on yearly and quarterly basis
and the way
this number has come around 101.2% and
104.5% quarter on quarter.  Here,
Clarity Infact,
these numbers are seen coming on a definitely strong scale.
A 45% upmove in the last session. Can the
uptrend continue?
If we look at the setup till yesterday, then as per the setup, there
is still a lower bottom setup.  I
feel that after this we may see an upmove out
which may see the stock
moving towards 1900 levels or even 1910.  There
is resistance around the 180 moving average.  I think
fresh buying can be avoided.  But if
someone has already bought then
profit booking can also be done around this level.
Because I feel that this may lead to
some improvement
in the coming days.  So one should
wait a little for fresh buying.  Below tip: If it
comes around 1800 then one should
try to enter there once again.  If
anyone has a long position then I think you should
think about booking profits around 900.
HDB Financials here posted a healthy quarter.
Asset quality has improved.
NI has risen almost 22% to
23.99.  If we talk about NIMS, it has
come at 8.23%.  PAT registered a jump of 41% and
reached around Rs 751 crore.
Talking about GNPA, it is seen coming at 2.44%
and NAPA has increased by about 1% here
on quarterly basis.  Ah, there was an
upmove of 5.25% in the last session, what should I do next
?
And yes, even now if we look at it, there is
still weakness on the long term charts but if we
look at it in the short term then a little more bounce can be
seen as per the charts
and I feel that
from a trading perspective for the short term, there can be an
opportunity to buy here, if we
get it today at the current levels, then
I feel that there is an
opportunity to buy here, the levels of 670 and 680 can be seen above and above that in the
short term,
after that, you can maintain a stop loss of
630 but still I feel that from a
short term perspective, you can
try a fresh buying
in HDF Financials.